Where are you going?
Khao Yai!
I just want to be with you.
Even though you'll get back with Jeen tomorrow,
I'll still be happy for today anyway.
So, you posted those pics...
just to get people to like you?
If that's all you want,
you can deactivate your account.
I can do it for you.
Where is Tee?
Hey, is he over there?
Tee!
Fuse!
Hey!
Tee!
Tee, are you okay?
You good? Are you okay?
Tee, you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm just practicing diving.
Oh.
You totally scared me.
Are you worried about me?
We'll leave then. Bye.
Don't play like this again.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
For frightening you.
Are you mad at me?
I'm not mad at you.
I'm just letting my mind wander.
When you disappeared,
I was so shocked.
And even more so when you're drowning.
I...
I only thought that I had to save you.
You must be fine.
If not, I'll...
I'm here.
I'm fine.
I already told you.
If you want me to stay,
I won't go anywhere.
Will you stay with me forever then?
Um.
I brought you some snacks from Khao Yai.
Did you go there?
Didn't you see that?
In his IG stories.
His stories are a whole row of dots.
Who did you go with?
My family.
You sure?
Is that so?
And Tee. Are you happy now?
Are you that close to him?
Yeah.
I've known you since grade 1
but you never invite me to join your family trip.
Because you're just a friend.
What is Tee, then?
I guess Tee is F...
WB.
FWB, my ass.
Did you hide yourself under my bed?
What do you mean?
I mean friends with buffets.
I also want to have one.
You don't need to eat buffets.
Just eat fish instead.
Fish?
This fish.
Hey, guys.
Up, up.
Damn.
Yay.
Fuse.
Hey, put me down.
Guys, Fuse's FWB is here.
Tee.
Do you like buffets?
Wit.
What did you ask him?
Huh?
Why?
Don't forget to have the snacks.
I chose them myself.
Hey, Tee.
How was the Khao Yai trip with my friend?
Do you enjoy?
I do.
Is my friend cute?
He's cute.
There you go.
Look at these.
They're exactly the same.
They're the same one.
Hey.
By the way, on the Khao Yai trip...
did you do the same thing
you did behind the building?
Huh? What?
What did they do?
Behind the building?
Hey, what did they do?
Spill the tea.
Behind the building,...
I saw them together and then...
Ouch.
Oh.
That's harsh.
So harsh.
Why is he acting like this?
What's wrong with him?
Go back to your seat.
Fine.
Okay.
What did you just do?
Why did you bring your bag?
I move to different rooms for every class.
Why aren't you in class yet?
Why did you stop by my room?
I just want to see you.
If I'm bothering you,
I'll leave.
Um.
Do you think you're cute when acting sulky?
Wanna grab dinner this evening?
Sure.
You promised.
Hey, Tee!
Tee!
We must go now.
I have to go.
Have a good day.
Okay.
See you this evening.
Bye.
Did you double-booked yourself?
What?
Ouch.
Nai asked me to tell you that
you have a practice this evening.
Huh?
Wanna grab dinner this evening?
You promised.
Hey, wait.
Yes?
You have a practice today, don't you?
Can I skip today's practice?
Can I go to Siam with my friend?
Why would you go there?
I want to watch a movie.
Don't even think about it, go back to practice.
Come here.
Hey, my shirt will tear.
Take your drum major mace out
It's too far.
Take it out.
If you came to practice more often,
it wouldn't be kept so far.
Are you okay?
You are so careless.
What would you do if I weren't here?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Does it hurt?
Where are you going?
To practice.
Why? Mhek is already there.
Hey, I'm the leader of cheer club.
Don't be stubborn.
Look at your wound. Stay right here.
Let me get you patched up.
Can you do it?
Easy peasy.
First, remove the dust.
Oh, isn't that too much?
Of course.
If you don't recover in time,
what will you do?
Let it get infected?
That way, you can't drag me to practice.
I still can drag you.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
my head would be cracked open.
Is there something on my face?
No.
You must clean the wound everyday,
so you'll recover soon.
Um.
One more thing.
I think you should take a break.
I'm really worried about you.
What if you slack off?
I won't slack off. I promise.
Rodtang.
Thanks.
Hey.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Hey, Nai will see it.
Damn.
The big day is around the corner.
You should practice.
Uh...
Your mace is over there.
Someone already brought it.
(Sorry, I have a practice.)
(Let's do it another time.)
Hey.
Fuse.
Are you the head drum major?
Are you the assistant drum major?
Um.
If I knew it's you,
I wouldn't skip any practice.
Whoa.
Let's practice.
Hey.
We must be the coolest
drum major in the school's history.
Let's get it.
You're really good at it.
You can do everything I taught you.
Hmm.
I have a secret.
What is it?
Wanna know?
Yeah.
My IQ is 180.
Maybe not.
What?
Come on.
(I just finished my extra class. I'm coming.)
Who are you talking to?
Nothing.
Just a peek.
Hey.
Hello, Tee.
Nai, why are you here?
What?
You little brat.
Hey.
Don't.
That's too tight.
What's wrong with you?
Hey.
It's uncomfortable.
You didn't look uncomfortable a moment ago.
Did you finish the extra class?
I also finished my practice.
Let's grab something to eat.
Can I join you two?
Sure, let's go.
Nai, will you come with us?
Nai doesn't want to go. It's fine.
I'll go.
Don't go.
He asked me.
No need to go.
Why would you go with us?
Because he invited me.
You don't have to go.
He invited me.
Just don't go.
I'll go.
Pizza delivery.
I didn't order it.
A promotion for today.
Buy one, get one free.
But if you are my boyfriend,
you can have it for free.
I don't want to eat it.
What?
So, what do you want to eat?
I'll order it for you.
I don't feel like eating.
And I want to be alone.
You can leave now.
Okay, fine.
Well, can you post any pic tonight?
Just post anything, I'll be the first who like it.
No.
I won't post any more pictures.
What?
Why?
Book.
(Tee 0 - 1 Rodtang)
Fuse, that restaurant is good.
Really?
(Tee 1 - 1 Rodtang)
Careful, watch where you're walking.
Nai, you okay?
Wanna piggyback?
My ass.
Right, Nai.
What happend to your leg?
It's nothing much.
Just something fell on me.
Who patched you up?
Hey, there is enough room for the four of us.
Let's head over.
Come on.
(Tee 1 -2 Rodtang)
Let's go.
(Tee 1 - 2 Rodtang)
(Tee 2 - 2 Rodtang)
It's too cold here. You'd better sit over there.
I don't think so.
(Tee 2 - 3 Rodtang)
Well, I'll sit with Rodtang.
Have you ever been to this restaurant?
I've never been here.
I'll order some food for you.
(Tee 2 - 4 Rodtang)
(Tee 3 - 4 Rodtang)
I'll take care of my person.
(Tee 3 - 5 Rodtang)
Why? I want to order some food for Fuse.
Hey, we'll order some food for you two.
You guys can wait here.
Alright.
Let's go, Tee.
What's wrong?
Don't you like Rodtang?
He keeps hanging around you.
Well, both of us are drum majors.
I think he definitely likes you.
Right, he told me that...
he's a fan of mine.
Because I'm handsome.
Then he must be a fan of mine too.
Because I'm more handsome than you.
No way.
Someone must think I'm more handsome than you.
Nah.
I think you're cute.
(Tee + 1,000)
What are you saying?
Let's buy some food.
I'm stuffed.
Who said don't want to have it earlier.
You stole all my food.
How do you guys get home?
I'll take the BTS.
Me too.
Fine.
What about you, Fuse?
I'll take the bus.
Let's split up here.
Goodbye.
Bye.
See you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Wanna piggyback?
I'm good.
You sure?
Yeah.
I want you to take a break.
Otherwise your wound might tear open.
It's fine.
It just feels a bit tight.
I think it'll be fine by tomorrow.
Let's call a temporary truce.
Fine.
Fuse and I practiced well today.
No need to worry.
If you guys practice,
I won't be worried at all.
But one try to come to Siam,
and the other try to leave to meet a partner.
Does Fuse have his happiness?
What?
His happiness.
When you're happy being with someone,
that person is your happiness.
Do you mean a partner?
Hey, I'm too young to know this stuff.
Fine.
Does Fuse have it? Who is his partner?
I don't know.
All I know is his partner goes to the other school.
And that person is freaking pretty.
Is his partner a girl?
Why?
I thought it's Tee.
Huh?
Tee?
Didn't you see?
Tee acted like a gatekeeper.
I couldn't even get near Fuse.
Wasn't he just teasing you?
I doubt it.
Well.
What about you?
Do you have a partner?
Fine.
Do you have your happiness?
Why? You don't like anyone?
Well, I like cute person and I like Fuse too.
So, do you prefer men or women?
These days, you can like whoever you want.
I like whoever catches my eyes.
That's great.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
Which station do you get off at?
Saint Louis station.
Oh.
Me too.
Which alley?
The alley that has a goddess shrine.
Hey, me too.
For real?
I'll come and hang out at your place a lot then.
Hang out? My house is not a kid playground.
Guys.
You are very attentive in class today,
so I won't give any homework.
Alright.
Teacher.
Yes?
What time is it?
Uh-oh.
It's already 12 PM.
Oh.
I'm hungry.
Well, let's take a lunch break.
Yay!
Fuse, how about some Mala today?
I have a practice.
Again?
You practice everyday.
It won't hurt to miss a practice just one day.
Being this hard-working is not yourself at all.
It's okay to take a break.
(Can we meet at your school this evening?
I want to watch you practice.)
(I probably not practice today.)
(Oh, I already ditched my friends' movie plan.)
Hey, Fuse.
Hey.
What's Robert's problem this time?
He wants to break up with his girlfriend.
Did he just realize that?
He realized it for a while,
but had no chance to do it.
So, what will you do next?
I need to break up with her.
It's starting to be unfair to her.
I do understand that...
she's done something unfair to you first.
But you shouldn't have done it like her.
Sort this out so your mind is at ease.
Being two-timing isn't cool at all.
Hey, not me.
I forgot, I mean Robert.
Um.
Okay.
I'll go back to our room, Fuse.
My bad, Robert Sae-tang.
Frame.
Huh?
Help me.
Don't.
Help you?
He is stealing my instant noodles.
I can't even help myself.
Do you need any help?
Help me? Just stop it.
What?
See? He's about to eat it.
Do you follow BKBOii?
Yeah, he's freaking sexy.
Do you know that he goes to our school?
Huh?
Who is he?
I don't know either. I'll look into it.
Why did you come outside?
Why did you follow me?
I told you not to talk to me at school.
Is it still in effect?
Why can we talk anywhere else,
but we can't talk here?
Then just don't talk to me.
Anywhere. Leave me alone.
Hey.
Fuse.
Have you been waiting for a while?
What did you buy?
Just in case you're hungry after practice.
Really?
But if you're not hungry, I'll have it.
Um.
It looks yummy.
You look like you don't really want to eat.
Tee.
Oh.
We bought the same thing.
It's yummy, right?
Um.
Did you buy it for Fuse?
Really?
You're so kind.
Let me see what you bought.
Wow, you actually got this one?
They're all gone when I went to get it.
I bet you probably bought them all.
Wow, my school is nothing like this.
You mean the smells?
Except Tee.
Because Tee smells so good.
What about me?
Fuse, I'll leave him to you.
Got it.
As you like.
Fire! Rodtang!
Gosh, fire!
Where is the water?
Put out the fire quickly!
Fuse, are you teasing me?
Um.
Because you slept.
Well, you teased me.
Um.
Alright.
Fuse, who is she?
Is she Tee's girlfriend?
Hey, she's my girlfriend.
Oh, hello.
How cute.
This is Jeen.
And this is Rodtang.
The head drum major of our school.
Wow.
You're so talented.
Not at all.
I'm just handsome.
Hey, come over here.
Let's practice.
Bring your mace.
Excuse me.
It's fine.
Tee, please take care of Jeen.
I've seen your happiness for the first time.
She's so cute.
What did you say again?
Your happiness.
What do you mean?
When you're happy with someone,
that person is your happiness.
What if I'm not happy?
Oh, you're not happy?
Uh.
I'm just asking.
You have to hold it like this to get a better grip.
And making your arms like this.
Sort this out
so your mind is at ease.
Being two-timing isn't cool at all.
Fuse, I got it.
You must not looking at
your happiness so that you can focus.
Turn this way.
I'll get you a mace.
Tee, you know what.
I've never seen Fuse being a drum major.
Have you ever seen it?
He looks so cool.
Good thing is there is no girls in this school.
If there were, it would bummed me out.
Why?
I'm afraid somone will take Fuse away from me.
It's a relief that there are only men here.
You're so cool, Fuse.
Have you finished the practice?
Um.
Great. My mom just called me to come home.
Is Tee going straight home?
Yeah, he is going home with me.
Okay, I have to go now.
Don't forget the snacks. Bye.
How was your talk with Jeen?
It was fun.
She's talkative.
You can pretend to sleep next time.
Will there be next time?
But...
Jeen is lovely. She seems to like you a lot.
You didn't get that matter wrong, did you?
You guys should talk things out nicely.
I don't think that would help.
It's not about her now.
It's my fault.
I think I'll break up with her.
In a few hours,
the friendly match will start.
Let's team up. One, two, three.
Aren't you a bit too handsome today?
I think I'm handsome everyday.
Can I persue you, the head of cheer club?
Why don't you sit with your friends?
I want to sit here.
Can I sit here?